{
  "students": [
    {
      "name": "mohamed",
      "email": "ali@ds",
      "password": "999",
      "id": 1,
      "subjects": [
        {
          "subjectname": "math",
          "id": "1",
          "degree": 1
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "name": "ahmed",
      "email": "ali@dsaa",
      "password": "444",
      "id": 2,
      "subjects": [
        {
          "subjectname": "english",
          "id": "2",
          "degree": 1
        },
        {
          "subjectname": "arabic",
          "id": "3",
          "degree": 0
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "name": "ali",
      "email": "ali@dsaasd",
      "password": "1234",
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "name": "samir",
      "email": "draz@gmail.com",
      "password": "01278654604",
      "id": 4,
      "subjects": [
        {
          "subjectname": "english",
          "id": "2",
          "degree": 0
        },
        {
          "subjectname": "math",
          "id": "1",
          "degree": 1
        },
        {
          "subjectname": "arabic",
          "id": "3",
          "degree": 0
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "name": "omar",
      "email": "sad@sad",
      "password": "111",
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "name": "abdo",
      "email": "sda@wq",
      "password": "888",
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "name": "islam",
      "email": "we@dsa",
      "password": "444",
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "name": "marwan",
      "email": "we@dsaaaaa",
      "password": "555",
      "id": 8
    }
  ],
  "doctor": [
    {
      "name": "admin",
      "email": "ali@dsa",
      "password": "0123",
      "id": "1"
    }
  ],
  "login": [
    {
      "username": "admin",
      "role": "doctor",
      "userid": "1",
      "id": "1"
    }
  ],
  "subject": [
    {
      "name": "math",
      "question": [
        {
          "name": "math",
          "question": " 1 * 1",
          "answer1": "1",
          "answer2": "3",
          "answer3": "2",
          "answer4": "4",
          "correctanswer": "1"
        },
        {
          "name": "math",
          "question": "2*2 +4",
          "answer1": "4",
          "answer2": "6",
          "answer3": "5",
          "answer4": "8",
          "correctanswer": "8"
        },
        {
          "name": "math",
          "question": "5*5",
          "answer1": "25",
          "answer2": "6",
          "answer3": "4",
          "answer4": "7",
          "correctanswer": "25"
        },
        {
          "name": "math",
          "question": "5/5*6",
          "answer1": "6",
          "answer2": "5",
          "answer3": "47",
          "answer4": "4",
          "correctanswer": "6"
        },
        {
          "name": "math",
          "question": "1+2-5*4",
          "answer1": "177",
          "answer2": "4",
          "answer3": "17",
          "answer4": "5",
          "correctanswer": "17"
        }
      ],
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "name": "english",
      "question": [
        {
          "name": "english",
          "question": "ewqewq",
          "answer1": "ewqewq",
          "answer2": "d",
          "answer3": "dsa",
          "answer4": "weewq",
          "correctanswer": "weewq"
        },
        {
          "name": "english",
          "question": "qwewq",
          "answer1": "erwe",
          "answer2": "rew",
          "answer3": "rq",
          "answer4": "ewr",
          "correctanswer": "erwe"
        },
        {
          "name": "english",
          "question": "rw",
          "answer1": "tet",
          "answer2": "te",
          "answer3": "456345",
          "answer4": "fgdgs",
          "correctanswer": "tet"
        },
        {
          "name": "english",
          "question": "tre",
          "answer1": "rweq",
          "answer2": "weqqwr",
          "answer3": "rwqew",
          "answer4": "rewwer",
          "correctanswer": "weqqwr"
        },
        {
          "name": "english",
          "question": null,
          "answer1": null,
          "answer2": null,
          "answer3": null,
          "answer4": null,
          "correctanswer": null
        },
        {
          "name": "english",
          "question": "oiuy",
          "answer1": "ui",
          "answer2": "k",
          "answer3": "iukllh",
          "answer4": "lhjkljkl",
          "correctanswer": "iukllh"
        }
      ],
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "name": "arabic",
      "question": [
        {
          "name": "arabic",
          "question": "ewqrewrqwe",
          "answer1": "rewr",
          "answer2": "ter",
          "answer3": "tretwewr",
          "answer4": "tewrtwert",
          "correctanswer": "ter"
        },
        {
          "name": "arabic",
          "question": "eqwe",
          "answer1": "rwet",
          "answer2": "t",
          "answer3": "ytru",
          "answer4": "urytutyuyt",
          "correctanswer": "rwet"
        },
        {
          "name": "arabic",
          "question": "hjg",
          "answer1": "hdhfdg",
          "answer2": "ytiuy",
          "answer3": "gf",
          "answer4": "tiyui",
          "correctanswer": "gf"
        },
        {
          "name": "arabic",
          "question": "op'/p[[p",
          "answer1": "p[",
          "answer2": "p[\\'o[",
          "answer3": "]po'p['",
          "answer4": "[o\\",
          "correctanswer": "[o\\"
        }
      ],
      "id": 3
    }
  ]
}